{
    "subject": "resource/Sentrigo",
    "predicate": "property/industry",
    "object": "resource/Software",
    "human_readable": "Sentrigo is in the software industry.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9289591312408447,
            "question": "What industry is Sentrigo part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9270456433296204,
            "question": "Could Sentrigo be considered a software company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8992533087730408,
            "question": "Is Sentrigo involved in the technology sector?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8752761483192444,
            "question": "How does Sentrigo's presence impact the software industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5809399485588074,
            "question": "What kind of products or services does Sentrigo likely offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2499413937330246,
            "question": "What are some challenges faced by companies in the software industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23366616666316986,
            "question": "What are some examples of other companies in the software industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21735674142837524,
            "question": "How has the software industry evolved over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19375795125961304,
            "question": "What skills are in demand for jobs in the software industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1407424509525299,
            "question": "What are the key trends shaping the future of the software industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sentrigo is in the software industry.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6144_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What skills are in demand for jobs in the software industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6144_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has the software industry evolved over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6144_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of other companies in the software industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6144_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6144_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6144_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6144_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6144_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6144_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6144_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6144_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6144_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6144_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6144_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents clearly state that Sentrigo is a provider of database security software.  This indicates it operates within the software industry. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because all the documents provided context information about Sentrigo, a provider of database security software, which suggests that they are indeed in the software industry."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Sentrigo, a company that develops and sells database security software solutions such as Hedgehog Enterprise, vPatch, and Repscan. This clearly indicates that Sentrigo operates within the software industry."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}